export const  greedytechniqueData = {
    definition : " A greedy technique, also known as the greedy algorithm, is an algorithmic paradigm that makes the locally optimal choice at each step in the hope of achieving the globally optimal solution. This approach aims to find the best solution by choosing the best option available at each stage, without considering the impact it might have on subsequent decisions.",
    explanation : [
        "Local Optimization: Greedy algorithms focus on making the best choice at each step, without considering the overall impact on the final solution.",
        "Constructive Approach: Greedy algorithms incrementally build a solution, adding elements one by one until the complete solution is obtained.",
        "No Backtracking: Once a decision is made, greedy algorithms do not revisit or change earlier choices.",
        "Efficient Implementation: Greedy algorithms are often simple and efficient to implement due to their local decision-making and lack of backtracking."
    ],
    questions: [
        {
            title: "Maximum Subarray",
            id:"53",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0053/?h=53",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Sum Circular Subarray",
            id:"918 ",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-sum-circular-subarray/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0918/?h=918",
        },
        {
            title: "Longest Turbulent Subarray",
            id:"978 ",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-turbulent-subarray/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0978/?h=978",
        },
        {
            title: "Jump Game",
            id:"55",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0055/?h=55",
        },
        {
            title: "Jump Game II",
            id:"54",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game-ii/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0045/?h=45",
        },
        {
            title: "Jump Game VII",
            id:"1871",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game-vii/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1871/?h=1871",
        },
        {
            title: "Gas Station",
            id:"134",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/gas-station/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0134/?h=134",
        },
        {
            title: "Hand of Straights",
            id:"846",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/hand-of-straights/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0846/?h=846",
        },
        {
            title: "Minimize Maximum of Array",
            id:"2439",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimize-maximum-of-array/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/2439/?h=2439",
        },
        {
            title: "Merge Triplets to Form Target Triplet",
            id:"1899",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-triplets-to-form-target-triplet/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1899/?h=1899",
        },
        {
            title: "Dota2 Senate",
            id:"649",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/dota2-senate/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0649/?h=649",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Points You Can Obtain from Cards",
            id:"1423",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-points-you-can-obtain-from-cards/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1423/?h=1423",
        },
        {
            title: "Partition Labels",
            id:"763",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-labels/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0763/?h=763",
        },
        {
            title: "Valid Parenthesis String",
            id:"678",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parenthesis-string/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0678/?h=678",
        },
        {
            title: "Eliminate Maximum Number of Monsters",
            id:"1921",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/eliminate-maximum-number-of-monsters/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1921/?h=1921",
        },
        {
            title: "Two City Scheduling",
            id:"1029",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-city-scheduling/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1029/?h=1029",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Length of Pair Chain",
            id:"646",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-length-of-pair-chain/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0646/?h=646",
        },
        {
            title: "Candy",
            id:"135",
            difficulty: "Hard",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/candy/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0135/?h=135",
        },
    ]
}